A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, Audiovisual Materials, RG 10 FA1318
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio Recordings, 1967-2004; 1; All items are 1/4 inch audio tape unless otherwise noted.
  - Conferences, Seminars, Lectures, and Meetings, 1967-2004; C
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (5), 1969 March 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 23 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8944)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Luncheon address by Barbara Ward, Lady Jackson.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (6), 1969 March 20; ¼ inch audio tape; 32 minutes (Box 13, Reel AV 15503)
      National Convocation on the U.S. and China - The Next Decade. Includes presentations by Franz Michael and Chester Cooper. Tape begins in the middle of a presentation.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (7), 1969 March 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 15 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8948)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (8) - Senator Edward Kennedy Address, 1969 March 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 21 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8950)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Dinner program - introduction by John D. Rockefeller 3rd, and first part of Senator Edward Kennedy's speech.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (9) - Senator Edward Kennedy Address (conclusion), 1969 March 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 28 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8951)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Dinner program - conclusion of Senator Edward Kennedy's speech.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (10), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 33 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8938)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Panel on China's economy and trade.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (11), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 32 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8941)
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (12), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; Tape 5 of 14 (Box 10, Reel AV 8942)
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (13), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 33 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8943)
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (14), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 33 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8945)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Panel on policy initiatives. Speakers John Fairbank and Theodore Sorensen.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (15), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 33 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8946)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Policy initiatives panel: Theodore Sorensen (continued), George Taylor, and Harrison Salisbury.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (16), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 32 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8947)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Policy intiiatives panel: Harrison Salisbury (continued), William Ruster, James C. Thomson, Jr.
    - Convocation on the U.S. and China (17), 1969 March 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 21 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8949)
      National Convocation on the U. S. and China - The Next Decade. Afternoon session, concluding question and answer period.
    - Robert Scalapino Views on China, circa 1970s; 15 minutes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12, Reel AV 9029)
      Inteview by Carolyn Lewis, on behalf of the League of Women Voters, Washington, DC, for the program "Perspective."
      The tape recording, labeled "Mainland China," begins in mid-response.
    - Roundtable on Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China, 1971 January 22-23; 1/4 inch audio tape; 6 hours 25 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9031)
      Unlabeled recording of the full day of sessions on Friday, January 22. See also separate recordings for Friday A.M. and Friday P.M. (AV 9034 and AV 9035).
    - Roundtable on Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China (Friday A.M.), 1971 January 22; 1/4 inch audio tape; 2 hours 54 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9034)
    - Roundtable on Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China (Friday P.M.), 1971 January 22; 1/4 inch audio tape; 3 hours 32 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9035)
    - Roundtable on Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China, 1971 January 23; 1/4 inch audio tape; 5 hours 15 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9033)
      Recording labeled "Sat X Press," presumably covering the second day of the National Committee's Roundtable meeting on January 23, 1971. The reference to "Press" may refer to the public summary session that closed the conference.
      See also file AV 9032 ("Press Conference") which appears to record the conference summation and closing discussions on Saturday, January 23.
    - Roundtable on Prospects and Problems of Developing Relations with China (Press Conference), 1971 January 22-23; 1/4 inch audio tape; 29 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9032)
    - Washington Press Symposium - Problems and Opportunities in Reporting about China, 1971 October 18; 1/4 inch audio tape; 179 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9038)
      China and the Press Symposium. Includes presentations by Donald Klein, David Mozingo, Robert Keatley, Stanley Karnow, A. Doak Barnett, and others. Tape does not appear to include the luncheon address by Norman Webster.
    - China's Economic and Social Development: An Inside View - Tape 2 of 4, 1972 February 16; 1/4 inch audio tape; 63 minutes (Box 12, Reel AV 9017)
      Second program in a lecture series at UCLA on "The China Riddle." Panel composed of Barry Richman, Jack Chen, and Richard Baum (moderator).
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1 of 7, 1972 September 19; 1/4 inch audio tape; 123 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8958)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2 of 7, 1972 September 19; 1/4 inch audio tape; 127 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8959)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3 of 7, 1972 September 19; 1/4 inch audio tape; 96 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8960)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4 of 7, 1972 September 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 85 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8961)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5 of 7, 1972 September 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 97 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8962)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6 of 7, 1972 September 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 127 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8963)
    - Exchanges with China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 7 of 7, 1972 September 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; Program recording, 13 minutes; tape runs for another 23 minutes. (Box 10, Reel AV 8964)
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 1 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8952)
      Conference at Columbia University cosponsored by the Academy of Political Science and the NCUSCR.
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 2 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8953)
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 3 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8954)
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 4 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8955)
      China's Development Experiment
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 5 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8956)
    - China's Developmental Experience - Tape 6 of 6 - Dub, 1972 October 26-28; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 10, Reel AV 8957)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1 of 8, 1973 April 28; 1/4 inch audio tape; 126 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8965)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2 of 8, 1973 April 28; 1/4 inch audio tape; 125 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8966)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3 of 8, 1973 April 28; 1/4 inch audio tape; 94 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8967)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4 of 8, 1973 April 28; 1/4 inch audio tape; 96 minutes (Box 10, Reel AV 8968)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5 of 8, 1973 April 28; ¼ inch audio tape; 95 minutes (Box 13, Reel AV 15500)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6 of 8, 1973 April 29; 1/4 inch audio tape; 93 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8969)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 7 of 8, 1973 April 29; 1/4 inch audio tape; 89 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8970)
    - Education in the People's Republic of China (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 8 of 8, 1973 April 29; 1/4 inch audio tape; 91 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8971)
    - Educators Delegation to the People's Republic of China, 1973 August 1-21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 60 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8973)
      This delegation of American teachers and educators toured China as guests of the Education Bureau of Peking. The recording is of an unidentified discussion period (via an interpreter) in which the delegates posed questions to their hosts concerning Chinese educational practices and experiences.
    - Educators Delegation to the People's Republic of China, 1973 August 1-21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 67 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8972)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1 of 8, 1974 May 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; 119 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8974)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2 of 8, 1974 May 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; 124 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8975)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3 of 8, 1974 May 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; 123 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8976)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4 of 8, 1974 May 6; 1/4 inch audio tape; 42 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8977)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5 of 8, 1974 May 7; 1/4 inch audio tape; 88 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8978)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6 of 8, 1974 May 7; 1/4 inch audio tape; 95 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8979)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 7 of 8, 1974 May 7; 1/4 inch audio tape; 117 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8980)
    - Prospects for U. S. - China Relations (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 8 of 8, 1974 May 7; 1/4 inch audio tape; 24 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8981)
    - Henry Kissinger Address to Members' Dinner, 1974 June 3; 1/4 inch audio tape; 7 minutes. (Box 12, Reel AV 9036)
      Tape labeled "SEC KISS #1." Kissinger spoke at the NCUSCR's members dinner, held jointly with the National Council for U.S. - China Trade and the Committee on Scholarly Communication with China.
    - Women in China, American Perspectives (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1 of 3, 1974 June 25; 117 minutes; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 11, Reel AV 8982)
    - Women in China, American Perspectives (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2 of 3, 1974 June 25; 1/4 inch audio tape; 110 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8983)
    - Women in China, American Perspectives (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3 of 3, 1974 June 25; 1/4 inch audio tape; 39 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8984)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1 of 6, 1977 February 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 118 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8985)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2 of 6, 1977 February 20; 1/4 inch audio tape; 115 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8986)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3 of 6, 1977 February 20-21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 124 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8987)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4 of 6, 1977 February 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 106 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8988)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5 of 6, 1977 February 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 122 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8989)
    - Exchange Experience with China: The Past, Present and Future (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6 of 6, 1977 February 21; 1/4 inch audio tape; 21 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8990)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 1 of 7, 1977 September 24; 1/4 inch audio tape; 104 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8991)
      Briefing for delegation to China, 1977 October 28 - Novemeber 14. Tapes labeled, U.S. Education Conference - China.
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 2 of 7, 1977 September 24; 1/4 inch audio tape; 110 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8992)
      Briefing for delegation to China, 1977 October 28 - Novemeber 14. Tape labeled, U.S. Education Conference - China.
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 3 of 7, 1977 September 24; 1/4 inch audio tape; 128 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8993)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 4 of 7, 1977 September 24; 1/4 inch audio tape; 117 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8994)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 5 of 7, 1977 September 24-25; 1/4 inch audio tape; 118 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8995)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 6 of 7, 1977 September 25; 1/4 inch audio tape; 129 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8996)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Briefing - Tape 7 of 7, 1977 September 25; 1/4 inch audio tape; 85 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8997)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 1 of 7, 1978 February 4; 1/4 inch audio tape; 126 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8998)
      Delegation to China, 1977 October 28 - November 14. Debriefing and preparation of report on "China's Schools in Flux." Tape labeled, China Conference.
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 2 of 7, 1978 February 4; 1/4 inch audio tape; 112 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 8999)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 3 of 7, 1978 February 4; 1/4 inch audio tape; 127 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 9000)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 4 of 7, 1978 February 4-5; 1/4 inch audio tape; 129 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 9001)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 5 of 7, 1978 February 5; 1/4 inch audio tape; 126 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 9002)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 6 of 7, 1978 February 5; 1/4 inch audio tape; 127 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 9003)
    - State Education Leaders Delegation - Wingspread Debriefing - Tape 7 of 7, 1978 February 5; 1/4 inch audio tape; 16 minutes (Box 11, Reel AV 9004)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1, 1988 August 8; 116 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15392)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2, 1988 August 9; 115 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15393)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3, 1988 August 9; 117 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15394)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4, 1988 August 9; 116 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15395)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5, 1988 August 9-10; 112 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15396)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6, 1988 August 10; 109 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15397)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 7, 1988 August 10; 115 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15398)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 8, 1988 August 10; 106 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15399)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 9, 1988 August 11; 113 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15400)
    - China's Development: Toward Defining an American Policy (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 10, 1988 August 11; 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15401)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 1, 1989 July 7; 115 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15402)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 2, 1989 July 8; 114 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15403)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 3, 1989 July 8; 114 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15404)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 4, 1989 July 8; 113 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15405)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 5, 1989 July 8; 102 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15406)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 6, 1989 July 8; 118 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15407)
    - China in Flux (Wingspread Conference) - Tape 7, 1989 July 9; 51 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15408)
    - Jonathan Spence Lecture, Annual Member's Meeting, 1991 February 25; 70 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15427)
      Meeting at Harvard Club, New York. Address on How (or Does?) History Helps Us Understand China and U.S.-China Relations.
    - Daniel Boorstin Talk, Beijing - Tape 1 of 2, 1992 April; 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15581)
      Lecture at the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs. Boorstin visited China and Hong Kong from March 30 - April 17, 1992.
    - Daniel Boorstin Talk, Beijing - Tape 2 of 2, 1992 April; 38 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 3, Tape AV 15582)
      Lecture at the Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs - question and answer period (continued).
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Shanghai Communique - Tape 1 of 2, 1997 February 20; 91 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15447)
      Plaza Hotel, New York. For a transcript of these tapes, see FA1189, RG 7, Series 13, box 46, folder 431.
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the Shanghai Communique - Tape 2 of 2, 1997 February 20; 7 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15448)
      Plaza Hotel (Baroque Room), New York. For a transcript of these tapes, see FA1189, RG 7, Series 13, box 46, folder 431.
    - James Schlesinger Address, Annual Members' Meeting, New York - Tape 1, 1997 November 17; 44 minutes (91 minutes total run time). There is pronounced background noise throughout the program recording.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15446)
      Meeting at the Plaza Hotel, New York.
      Schlesinger's address is found on the first 44 minutes of the recording; thereafter, the recording switches abruptly to a music program on CBS FM radio.
    - Premier Zhu Rongji Speech (Voice of America), 1999 April 9; 56 minutes. There is a brief interruption in the recording at around 46 minutes.; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15513)
      Tape 1 of 1. Dinner in honor of Premier Zhu Rongji, in Washington, DC. Cosponsored by the NCUSCR, the America-China Society, the Asia Society, the Committee of 100, the Council on Foreign Relations, the U. S. - China Policy Foundation, and the U. S. Chamber of Commerce. Address delivered in Chinese, with translation into English.
      The recording cuts off abruptly at the end (during a question and answer period).
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session One - Tape 2 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15523)
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Sessions One and Two - Tape 3 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15524)
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Two - Tape 1 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 25 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15522)
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Three - Tape 4 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15525)
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Three, and Luncheon Address by Senator Dianne Feinstein - Tape 5 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15526)
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Four - Tape 6 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15527)
      Discussion of military and political issues vis-a-vis China.
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Five - Tape 7 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15528)
      Discussion of Human Rights issues. Tape begins with continuing discussion (from Session 4?) of economic and trade issues.
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations, Session Six - Tape 8 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15529)
      Continuation of Human Rights discussion (Session 5?) and wrap-up discussion concerning policy recommendations.
    - Airlie Conference on the Future of U.S.-China Relations - Tape 9 of 9, 1999 July 25-27; 56 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15530)
      Conclusion of wrap-up discussion (Session 6?).
    - National Committee on United States-China Relations Gala Dinner, 1999 September 8; 72 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15532)
      Speaker, Henry Kissinger.
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Annual Members' Address, New York City, 1999 November 18; 85 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15514)
      Address by panel composed of Winston Lord, J. Stapleton Roy, and James Sasser.
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Board Meeting - Tape 1 of 4, 1999 November 19; 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15516)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Board Meeting - Tape 2 of 4, 1999 November 19; 93 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15517)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Board Meeting - Tape 3 of 4, 1999 November 19; 92 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15518)
    - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations Board Meeting - Tape 4 of 4, 1999 November 19; 6 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15519)
    - National Committee on United States - China Relations, Annual Members' Meeting Program, 2000; 102 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15535)
      Tape 1 of 1. Panel discussion.
    - Ambassador Joseph W. Prueher Address- Tape 1 of 2, 2000 March 2; 45 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15520)
      Prueher spoke on U.S. relations with China at a luncheon in New York cosponsored by the Asia Society and the National Committee.
    - Ambassador Joseph W. Prueher Address - Tape 2 of 2, 2000 March 2; 8 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15521)
      Questions and answers. Prueher spoke on U.S. relations with China at a luncheon in New York cosponsored by the Asia Society and the National Committee.
    - Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role - Tape 1 of 9, 2000 July 14-16; 95 minutes (the program begins at minute 7).; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 2, Tape AV 15536)
      Pocantico Conference Center. Tape titled US-Taiwan Relations.